The following programme contains
strong language and adult themes.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Shit!
Remember.
you've got to bring your gloves.
Yes.
I'd do your coat up. darling.
Woah! Cool!
Miss. Miss!
Yes?
Watch! He's really class.
You watching?
I'm watching.
Come on then. Cefin. show me.
Let's see. Cefin.
Go on. Cefin!
It's a normal bottle...
and as you push around it.
and it comes straight through!
Cool!
You're a very talented
magician. Cefin.
Thank you. Miss Ellis.
Let me see that.
Who else has got tricks?
Nobody? Gosh. you need
to get some lessons.
Did you make this?
Yeah.
Did you? It's very clever.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Ooh. let me look at that sting.
Ohh. We'll have to put something
on that when we get inside.
Thank you. Miss.
Miss Ellis.
I had the nightmare again.
The black sow chased me
into the water and I drowned.
James. what happens when you get
stung during the day.
what happens to it at night?
It itches.
Yeah.
OK. dreams can be a bit like that.
If something frightens you
during the day.
at night it can come back
and scare you.
But...
...if you face up to your fears
during the day.
they can't get you at night.
D'you understand?
Mm-hmm.
You will all face devastation!
Poisoned water.
Poisoned air.
Nisha?
21 species were lost last year.
Come on. kids. It's alright.
Everyone inside.
Back into the classroom. please.
Osian is a weirdo!
Osian!
Kids. this way. please.
Let go of him. Let him go!
Look at him. look what you're...
Are you alright?
Yeah.
OK. go inside.
I'll be there in a minute.
Go to Mrs Jones. Don't worry. Cefin.
He should be worried.
OK. come on.
All of them should.
No. he shouldn't. He's nine.
You cannot do this at a school.
you cannot grab a child. Osian.
Osian. it's Jackie.
You've spoken to me
about your ideas before.
I know who...
It's important for people
to understand.
I know.
Here.
You just...
You can't do it here.
Osian. I'm gonna call your sister
and I'm going to tell her
that you're on your way home
and she's gonna put the kettle on.
If you're not back at The Ship
in ten minutes...
...I'm gonna call social services. OK?
Just go home.
You'll see at the meeting.
Jackie Ellis.
There's no way out.
No... way out.
Go home.
Yeah. maybe we should
think about teaching it.
We're not adding population control
to the curriculum.
Testing... Testing. one. two.
Alright!
Can you hear?
Thank you!
Quiet!
Can you hear me?
-Yes!
- Right.
OK. yes. I know I've been
up here a fair few times before.
you've all seen me before. but...
I've got news this time.
Money for the sea wall. is it?
Bringing the library back?
Right. OK. so. I know
you've raised a lot of money
for the sea wall. alright?
Yeah. and work has already started.
About time!
But...
it's not gonna be enough.
Why not?
We have to relocate you
outside of Morfa.
What are you talking about?
Alright. you do it. I can't.
Listen. Please
Leave? Where?
Listen. you're out of time. OK?!
We survived the storm
five years ago.
This winter is different.
OK. surges from storms
could raise sea levels
by five to six meters.
Oh. come on!
It will completely cover
the causeway. cut you off.
and when a storm...
Listen. now...
When a storm like that hits.
this entire town will be underwater.
Not with our sea wall!
Now. you need to properly
face the idea of leaving this place.
You cannot win a war against water.
You can't just keep building
bigger and bigger sea walls.
That's exactly
what we're doing.
We're building the wall.
we're finishing the wall.
and it'll protect the town.
Listen! We're not scared
and we are not leaving!
What's wrong with all of you?!
Look. you see this? You see it?
Eh?!
Our sheep have grazed this land
for over 500 years and they're
not going anywhere. I can tell you!
Eh?
Right?
Too right.
WE are not going anywhere.
Long live Morfa!
Hmm!
Not here.
Follow me.
No. no. no!
No! No. Cefin! No!
Oh. my God!
No! No! Cefin!
Emergency.
Which service do you require?
Ambulance.
Connecting you now.
Hello. What's your location?
I'm in Morfa Halen.
Morfa Halen?
In a ditch by Williams Street.
Is the patient awake?
No.
Is the patient breathing?
OK. The tide's high.
the causeway's shut.
We'll send the Community
First Responder immediately.
- Oh. my God!
- Can you stay
with the patient until they arrive?
♪ Night after sorrow
♪ You're my song
♪ Strings will collide
♪ We are undone
♪ Darken the waters
♪ Deepen regrets
♪ Better to remember
♪ Or better to forget. ♪
Really are being treated
to some beautiful scenes today.
Just look at the Adelaide hills.
It's stunning.
Stunning weather here today.
I mean. we can see it's a little
tricky with the wind
whipping through the top
of the eucalyptus there.
coming from left to right.
over the shoulders of the riders.
Don't really get what you
get from watching this.
It's so boring!
I know. it's boring. isn't it?!
That'll be him now.
Oh. Jack.
Uh. now's really not a good time.
I was expecting Cefin home.
I need to talk to you. Shell.
Jackie. are you OK? Come in.
Dan.
God. Jack. come in.
Come in.
Boys. let's. um...
Let's go and get ready for bed. eh?
It's got five minutes.
No. no. no. we're not
- arguing about this. Go on.
- Go on.
We need to help Jackie.
Go on.
Come in. Jack. Sit down.
OK? What's happened?
Um... Sit down.
I don't want the boys to hear us.
Oh. don't worry about them.
You feeling OK? I thought
you were doing alright. Jack.
I'm gonna call your dad. OK?
No. listen.
I'm really sorry that I'm going
to have to tell you this.
But I just found Cefin.
I found him in a drainage ditch.
I think he's...
I think he drowned. Shell.
Is this some kind of joke?
The police. they're on their way.
And they sent the First Responder.
so Ira's with him now.
This is some kind of sick joke.
Danny? What the hell?
The police would be here.
They're on their way. Shell.
No.
I'm sorry.
Uh... I'll get...
We'll go. We'll go.
No. we're not leaving.
He'll be back. He'll be hungry.
He'll want his dinner.
Shell. we've got to go. Now!
I'm not going anywhere.
He'll be back...
Put that down. We've got to go now.
Put it down. Put it down!
- Get your coat on.
- Danny...
Where is he?
...you should wait for the police.
- Where is he?
- He's at
Williams Street. in the ditch.
Let's go. let's go. now.
You stay here.
You watch the boys. You don't
say a word to them. alright?
Let's go. Shell. now. Let's go.
It's not that deep.
A foot in the middle?
You should be alright in that.
What's in the truck?
Rubble. From the sea defences.
What. d'you work on the site?
Nah. I just do the haulage.
Samphire. It's delicious.
What's all this?
They're with me.
Detective Sergeant Bull.
Can you stay there for a sec for me?
You got Forensics? The photographer?
Yeah. Not far behind us. Boss.
I heard it was a child.
Yeah.
Is it Nessa Taman?
No. Male.
Danny. Shell.
the police are here now.
You have to leave him.
Come on.
I'm Detective Bull.
Now. here's what's gonna happen;
I've got two police officers here.
they're gonna take care of you.
then we've got two paramedics
who are gonna take care of your boy.
They'll take care of him?
I promise you they will.
Can you promise me they will?
I promise. but we're gonna
get you out of the ditch.
Can you help them out. please?
- - Come on.
- Get 'em out.
- Come on.
There you... There you go.
Jesus Christ.
That's it.
Shell. Shell. come 'ere.
Shell. come 'ere.
No. no. no. no. no. they're
gonna look after him. darling.
It's OK. It's OK.
They're gonna look after him.
Deng's gonna take care of you.
Come with me. I'm Detective Deng.
We're gonna get you back home.
Dr Taman.
Detective.
Did you discover the body?
No. I'm the First Responder.
Jackie found him.
Jackie Ellis?
Yes.
Where is she now?
I'm not sure.
Fuck.
Uh. yeah. hi.
Can you. uh... Can you put me through
to the Superintendent's office?
Oh. fuck.
Well. she needs to call
me back immediately. alright?
Eric Bull cannot
be handling this case.
Hiya.
Hey.
Listen. we've got
a heavy downpour forecast tonight.
so all this evidence
is gonna get washed away.
I need every millimetre scoured.
D'you understand?
Yeah.
Have you found anything
to suggest it's not an accident?
Uh. no. Just...
this handprint.
which we're struggling with.
And. um. the Hills
said they sent him to school
in blue wellies.
but we haven't found them.
OK.
Um. I. uh...
I hear Jackie Ellis found the body.
Has she given a statement?
Not yet. no.
I could do it.
No. I'll do it. thank you.
OK. We're in a meadow
on the edge of Morfa Halen.
Wooden boardwalk.
We have Hedge Mustard.
Prolific cord grass. Honey fungus.
Blackberry bush.
Salt burned.
Have you sampled this water yet.
in the ditch?
Uh. we've sent it off
to the lab. yeah.
Can you PH test it
for me now. please? Ta.
Jones. get a PH test.
Um... It's seawater.
Mm. I thought so. yeah.
I don't understand.
It's a rainwater ditch.
Yeah. When's the body
going up for postmortem?
In the next hour.
Could you send a sample with it
- as well. please.
- Yeah.
Can somebody tag
this measuring pole for me?
And find out who owns it.
Hello.
Hello. love.
Go sit down.
It just brings it all back.
doesn't it?
I can't help but think
of our little niece.
Have the police spoken to you yet?
Uh. yeah. They're piecing together
Cefin's last movements.
Hey. um. look. I've...
I've decided not to tell the kids.
We'll send them home with letters.
let the parents tell them tonight.
Yeah. thanks.
OK.
OK. everyone.
It's a beach day today.
Are you in Jackie Ellis' class?
Is that the same class
as Cefin Hill?
Cefin's my best friend.
But he's not here today.
OK.
Why are you not out there
with the rest of them?
I got stung by a bee.
Stung by a bee?
Let's have a look.
Oh. yeah.
What's your name?
James Rees.
So. you and your best mate Cefin.
after school.
where do you go and play?
Sometimes at the farm.
The farm?
Is that Solomon Bevan's farm?
Cefin's Grandad?
It is?
And were you with him
after school yesterday?
You were? After school?
Bull!
Get away from him.
Where did you go?
Bull!
Did you go to the farm?
Step away. Bull. Get away!
James. come here. Come to me.
Ellis.
Questioning a child
unaccompanied. Nice.
I need to take a statement.
Right. James.
You see where Mr Waerea is?
I want you to run as fast
as you can to him.
Go on. good lad.
Listen. I should...
I should've taken a statement
from you last night. listen.
a first account. at least.
but you disappeared
after you'd been at Cefin's house.
Informing the family
is police business. you know that.
Don't give me that bollocks.
Listen. when a young boy
has been found dead.
everything is police business. OK?
Do you mean Cefin?
Bloody 'ell.
It's alright. James.
Who's been found dead?
It's gonna be OK.
Where's Cefin?
I'll be right behind you. OK?
Run to him.
I can't believe they sent you.
You are not the right
person for this.
I need you to stay away
from this beach... Mm-hmm.
...from these children.
and you stay away from me.
Bull!
I'm gonna come and get
your statement after school
at three-thirty.
On the dot!
They sent you. did they?
Dylan Rees.
Yeah. that's my name.
That's good detective work.
Keep it up.
Hello. can I help you?
Oh. yeah. I'm Detective Bull.
I'm investigating
the death of Cefin Hill.
I understand that you work for the
Wales Environment Institute?
Uh. yes. Yeah. I do.
Sorry. have we met before?
I was on the. uh...
Nessa Taman investigation
a few years ago.
so I was in and out back then.
No. yeah.
I. um... Well. I only
moved here six months ago. so...
Do you mind if I ask you
a few initial questions?
Come in. yeah.
Cheers.
Was anyone working
in the area around the. uh...
footpath that runs along
the drainage ditches yesterday?
Oh. God. is that where he died?
Uh. no. No one was working there.
It was just me and. um...
I was over in the estuary
in the morning and then I was...
I was with the Councillor
from lunchtime.
So sorry. Are you sure
we haven't met before?
What time did you leave
the Councillor approximately?
It would've been around. um. 8pm.
after the meeting.
8pm. OK. And someone
can corroborate that. can they?
Yeah.
How do they work.
these. uh. these ditches?
Uh. to help with the flooding.
they uh...
they drain the rainwater
coming off the top of the mountain.
and then they channel it
all around the town.
OK. and you check on them. do you?
Monitor 'em. that sort of thing?
Only sporadically. yeah.
It's just I found one of your poles.
At the scene.
OK. well...
it's probably there from last spring
when we dredged them.
OK. And there was seawater
in the ditch that runs along
the footpath.
- Seawater?
- Yeah.
No. that's not possible. no.
So they drain rainwater and...
they're about a mile
away from the sea.
Are you going somewhere?
Uh. no. I just haven't unpacked.
What. in six months?
Well. I'm here for a job.
I'm not making a home.
And what exactly is that job?
What's the nature of it?
So. I monitor sea levels. surges.
um. tides.
y'know that sort of thing.
Flagging problems ahead of time.
What about the. um...
the rain tonight.
Is that gonna be a problem?
Tonight's normal. but it will flood.
So. yeah. I would park your car
up at the um. the forest carpark.
not The Ship. if I were you.
Got it. OK.
I-I remember you.
Is it Eric?
Oh. my God. It is you. I knew it.
Wow. um...
What... What was that?
Um. three years ago now?
Four?
OK. yeah. Well. I'll. uh...
I'll be in touch
if I need anymore assistance or...
OK?
Um. right. yeah.
Jackie?
Jackie Ellis?!
Hey. Dad.
Ohh!
I'm sorry it was you who found him.
Yeah.
What a terrible thing.
Blight.
The spores blow in
with the wind and the rain
and you just can't stop it.
We're gonna be alright. Dad.
Yeah.
Bull called by looking for you.
He came late last night.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think he'd have
the nerve come here.
No.
Have you spoken to Lydia?
Dad. did you tell her?
Did you tell her about Cefin?
Your sister doesn't need to know.
He was the same age as Nessa. Dad.
Don't let this take you
back there. Jackie.
You've been doing so well.
Alright. Detective Eric Bull.
I was wondering if Cheryl
and Danny Hill are in?
Everyone's in.
Good afternoon.
I'm Detective Bull.
Uh. and I am just here today
to ascertain
Cefin's movements
from when he left school
until seven-thirty
on Thursday. when he. uh...
when he was found.
Now. if any of you saw anything.
then please do come forward.
Now. I'm gonna be speaking
to you all individually.
obviously. but. um.
the sooner I can get
any information. the better.
So. it's an investigation. is it?
You don't think it was an accident?
This is just normal procedure.
We welcome "normal procedure..."
...but if you're thinking
of investigating this family...
It's just normal procedure
to question the family at this stage
when the cause of death
is still unclear.
Yeah. well. you've already destroyed
one family with your investigation.
Hmm?
So if you dare point a finger
at anyone in this room.
I can assure you
you'll be sorry. eh?
Very. very sorry.
OK.
I'm gonna leave my details here.
So. if you can think of anything.
then please don't hesitate
to get in touch.
Thank you for your time.
I'm sorry. Jackie. It's terrible.
Yeah. It is.
I mean. an accident like that.
it doesn't happen.
He was a smart kid.
I need to take a statement from you.
Well. I'm getting my tea
right now. so...
Listen if you don't
want to do it here.
then we can go
to the station tonight.
There you are.
Thank you.
No. no. It's on the house.
Well. one for him then.
I don't want anything.
Look. we can do it
in the car now. come on.
What an offer
Look. you're not the only one
who's had a bad day y'know.
if that's any consolation to ya.
You know.
I think you've got more charming.
Come in the car with me now.
we'll get it over and done-
Hey. Detective?
Haddock and chips. right?
Oh. right. yeah. ta.
You told my nephew
that his best friend was dead.
What kind of a person does that?
You need to go home
and sleep it off. alright?
Fucking bastard!
Dylan. stop! Dylan!
- He's a fucking bastard!
- Stop!
He told James about Cefin.
It's not right.
Stop! He didn't.
Yes. he fucking did.
He didn't. I did.
Alright? I didn't mean to.
but it was me.
That was impressive for a
- primary school teacher.
- Piss off.
Come in the car with me.
And then I called it in.
Ira got there
about ten minutes later.
She's been the First Responder
for the past few years.
And the body was against the bank
the whole time. was it?
I tried my best to preserve the bank.
It was really muddy.
There was a handprint.
You saw that. right?
And then what happened?
You think he was murdered?
Could you please continue
with your statement.
The police aren't always
that sensitive.
so I went to see the parents.
They're old friends.
Informing the family
is police business. Ellis.
And in case you hadn't noticed.
you're not in the Police anymore.
are ya?
Fuck off.
That first meeting is vital
in determining whether or not
anyone was involved.
You know I was your supervisor?
Have you forgotten?
You don't need to lecture me.
Can we not make this personal?
Is that OK?
You just don't understand
anything. do you?
Can't get it through that
thick fucking skull of yours.
Because some things sometimes. Bull.
y'know they can be personal.
They can be fucking personal.
And what was their reaction
when you told them?
They were upset.
Why did you lie to Dylan for me?
About what happened on the beach?
I heard you tell him that it was you
that told James about Cefin.
After I informed the parents.
they wanted to go see the body.
I stayed and looked after
Cefin's brothers.
And when they returned I went home.
No. you didn't go home.
Then I went home.
And what about Osian Northam?
Osian?
Yeah.
Osian is not a suspect.
He's harmless.
A witness saw him grab Cefin's arm.
Can I go now?
Why did you lie
to Dylan for me? Why?
Because believe it or not. Bull. I
would like this case solved. alright?
I would like what is best
for this place.
I wanna do the right thing by Cefin.
and I would like to find out
what happened to Nessa.
The more you are hated.
the less likely it is
that you can do your fucking job.
You should never have left
the force. Ellis.
Yeah. well...
It got a bit personal.
though. didn't it?
My partner. who I worked with
every single day. who had my back.
who I trusted with my entire life.
fucked it up when they betrayed me.
So. yeah. it got a bit tricky.
Still no apology.
Eric!
I've got more rain gear
in my car if you want?
Normal rain. you said?
It's only spitting a little.
But there is more coming though.
There's a system everyone's
been watching in the Gulf of Mexico.
If storms like that
develop on this coast. well.
it'll be big.
How big?
Emergency evacuation big.
Really?
Definitely.
Take them off on the lino.
And the shirt.
And the trousers.
What?
Eric Bull. I am not a pervert.
Your trousers are wet
and I'm going to put them
in the dryer.
Irene.
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
Bull?
Hello?
Look. I'm gonna call you back
from the landline.
- Bull?
- I'll call you back from...
Uh...
- - Irene?
- Bull?
- Hiya. Go on.
I had a look at your
- unexpected death.
- Yeah.
Can we meet?
Uh. well. I'm in Morfa.
Causeway's closed.
The tide's high.
Right. Bee sting on his neck.
Yeah.
We found a hair on his
T-shirt that isn't his.
I sent off the eyes.
His eyes?
The whites are yellow.
We've sent it all for testing.
No signs of sexual abuse.
Initial thoughts were accidental
drowning. larynx spasm.
lungs full of water.
But the thing is-
The water in his lungs
doesn't match the sample. does it?
- Exactly.
- No.
The sample's seawater.
And the water in his lungs
is fresh water. So...
So someone's moved the body
to make it look like an accident.
That ditch is not where Cefin died.
No. I'll go there now.
Subtitles by Sky Access Services
www.skyaccessibility.sky
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-